# Changers Lorgs!

## 1.0

Full rewrite.  Essentially a brand new module.

- Return a promise instead of taking a callback.
- Use native `fs.mkdir(path, { recursive: true })` when available.
- Drop support for outdated Node.js versions.  (Technically still works on
  Node.js v8, but only 10 and above are officially supported.)

## 0.x

Original and most widely used recursive directory creation implementation
in JavaScript, dating back to 2010.
