/*! *****************************************************************************
Copyright (c) Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved.
Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License"); you may not use
this file except in compliance with the License. You may obtain a copy of the
License at http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

THIS CODE IS PROVIDED ON AN *AS IS* BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY
KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION ANY IMPLIED
WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF TITLE, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE,
MERCHANTABLITY OR NON-INFRINGEMENT.

See the Apache Version 2.0 License for specific language governing permissions
and limitations under the License.
***************************************************************************** */


/// <reference no-default-lib="true"/>

declare namespace Intl {
    /**
     * The `Intl.getCanonicalLocales()` method returns an array containing
     * the canonical locale names. Duplicates will be omitted and elements
     * will be validated as structurally valid language tags.
     *
     * [MDN](https://developer.mozilla.org/docs/Web/JavaScript/Reference/Global_Objects/Intl/getCanonicalLocales)
     *
     * @param locale A list of String values for which to get the canonical locale names
     * @returns An array containing the canonical and validated locale names.
     */
    function getCanonicalLocales(locale?: string | readonly string[]): string[];
}
